Guide to the Theodore W. "Ted" Minah Records and Papers,1941-1975 and undated
Duke University. University Archives
- Administrative Records,1945-1975 and undated
  - General Administrative Records,1945-1975 and undated
    - Oak Room Renovations, 1950-1962 (Box 16)
    - Oak Room Sales Study, 1947-1957 (Box 16)
    - Office of Information Services (Box 16)
    - Operation Statements (Box 16)
    - Operating Percentages (Ideal) (Box 16)
    - Operating Statements – Graduate Center Dining Halls, 1954-1955 (Box 17)
    - Operating Statements – Graduate Center Dining Halls, 1955-1956 (Box 17)
    - Operating Statements – Graduate Center Dining Halls, 1956-1957 (Box 17)
    - Operating Statements – Graduate Center Dining Halls, 1957-1958 (Box 17)
    - Operating Statements – Graduate Center Dining Halls, 1958-1959 (Box 17)
    - Operating Statements – Graduate Center Dining Halls, 1960-1961 (Box 17)
    - Operating Statements – Graduate Center Dining Halls, 1961-1962 (Box 17)
    - Operating Statements – Graduate Center Dining Halls, 1962-1963 (Box 17)
    - Operating Statements – Graduate Center Dining Halls, 1963-1964 (Box 17)
    - Operating Statements – Graduate Center Dining Halls, 1964-1965 (Box 17)
    - Operating Statements – Graduate Center Dining Halls, 1965-1966 (Box 17)
    - Operating Statements – Graduate Center Dining Halls, 1966-1967 (Box 17)
    - Operating Statements – Graduate Center Dining Halls, 1967-1968 (Box 17)
    - Operating Statements – Graduate Center Dining Halls, 1968-1969 (Box 18)
    - Operating Statements – Graduate Center Dining Halls, 1969-1970 (Box 18)
    - Operating Statements – Graduate Center Dining Halls, 1970-1971 (Box 18)
    - Operating Statements – Graduate Center Dining Halls, 1971-1972 (Box 18)
    - Operating Statements – Graduate Center Dining Halls, 1972-1973 (Box 18)
    - Operating Statements – Graduate Center Dining Halls, 1973-1974 (Box 18)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1946-1950 (Box 18)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1949-1950 (Box 18)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1954-1955 (Box 18)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1955-1956 (Box 18)
    - Operating Statements (Profit/Loss) – Men’s Dining Halls, 1954-1959 (Box 18)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1956-1957 (Box 18)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1957-1958 (Box 19)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1958-1959 (Box 19)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1959-1960 (Box 19)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1960-1961 (Box 19)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1961-1962 (Box 19)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1962-1963 (Box 19)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1963-1964 (Box 19)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1964-1965 (Box 19)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1965-1966 (Box 19)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1966-1967 (Box 19)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1967-1968 (Box 20)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1968-1969 (Box 20)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1969-1970 (Box 20)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1970-1971 (Box 20)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1971-1972 (Box 20)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1972-1973 (Box 20)
    - Operating Statements – Men’s Dining Halls, 1973-1974 (Box 20)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1948-1951 (Box 20)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1951-1952 (Box 20)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1952-1953 (Box 20)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1953-1954 (Box 20)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1954-1955 (Box 20)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1955-1956 (Box 21)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1956-1957 (Box 21)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1957-1958 (Box 21)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1958-1959 (Box 21)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1959-1960 (Box 21)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1960-1961 (Box 21)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1961-1962 (Box 21)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1962-1963 (Box 21)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1963-1964 (Box 21)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1964-1965 (Box 21)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1965-1966 (Box 21)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1966-1967 (Box 21)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1967-1968 (Box 22)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1968-1969 (Box 22)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1969-1970 (Box 22)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1971-1972 (Box 22)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1972-1973 (Box 22)
    - Operating Statements – Women’s College Dining Halls, 1973-1974 (Box 22)
    - Organic/Health Foods (Box 23)
    - Organization – Business Division (Box 23)
    - Organization – East Campus (Box 23)
    - Organization – West Campus (Selling & Service) (Box 23)
    - Organization – West Campus Personnel (Box 23)
    - Organization Chart – Dining Halls (Box 23)
    - Organization Chart – Duke University (Box 23)
    - Organizations (Campus), 1964-1966 (Box 23)
    - Orientation, 1967, 1972 (Box 23)
    - Orientation Program in American Law (ORAL), 1969 (Box 23)
    - Pan-Afro Training Camp, 1971 (Box 23)
    - Parking – Rear of C.A. Dukes Building (Box 23)
    - Parking Regulations (Box 23)
    - Passover Week (Box 23)
    - Payroll Comparisons, 1960-1961 (Box 23)
    - Payroll Comparisons, 1961-1962 (Box 23)
    - Payroll Comparisons, 1962-1963 (Box 23)
    - Payroll Comparisons, 1963-1964 (Box 23)
    - Payroll Comparisons, 1964-1965 (Box 23)
    - Payroll Comparisons, 1965-1966 (Box 23)
    - Payroll Comparisons – East Campus (Box 23)
    - Payroll Data, 1970-1973 (Box 23)
    - Payroll Department Memos (Box 23)
    - Payroll Procedure – I.B.M. (Box 23)
    - Peat, Marwick, Mitchell & Co. – Cash Statements (Box 23)
    - [The] Peer, 1954 Spring (Box 23)
    - Pepsi-Cola Contest, 1969 Aug (Box 23)
    - Personnel (Box 23)
    - Personnel Chart – Duke University Dining Halls (Box 23)
    - Personnel Department (Box 23)
    - Personnel Notices – Duke University (Box 24)
    - Personnel Organization (Notices, etc.) (Box 24)
    - Personnel Study (Box 24)
    - Personnel Study Man Hours, 1949-1961 (Box 24)
    - Photo, 1949 (Box 24)
    - Photo – AA Steak Dinner, undated (Box 24)
    - Photo – Cooking Turkeys (West Campus), undated (Box 24)
    - Photo – Crabtree Park (Minahs), undated (Box 24)
    - Photo – Durham Restaurant Association, undated (Box 24)
    - Photo – [Mrs.] Gibb’s Wedding Cake, undated (Box 24)
    - Photo – Institution Magazine Award, 1960 (Box 24)
    - Photo – Johnny Long Reception, undated (Box 24)
    - Photo – National Restaurant Show, undated (Box 24)
    - Photos – Beaufort Marine Lab Dorms & Kitchen Building (Box 24)
    - Photos – Blue & White Room Serving Area, undated (Box 24)
    - Photos – Christmas Decorations, undated (Box 24)
    - Photos – East Campus for Institutions Magazine Contest, 1955 (Box 24)
    - Photos – Food Production (West Campus), undated (Box 24)
    - Photos – Gilbert-Addoms, undated (Box 24)
    - Photos – Gold Cup Award, undated (Box 24)
    - Photos – Graduate Center, undated (Box 24)
    - Photos – Graduate Center, undated (Box 24)
    - Photos – Help’s Christmas Party – West Campus, undated (Box 24)
    - Photos – Meat Inspection, 1953 (Box 24)
    - Photos – Men’s Dining Halls – Dishwashing Machine, undated (Box 24)
    - Photos – Mendenhall’s Class, undated (Box 24)
    - Photos – National Hotel Exposition, 1950 (Box 24)
    - Photos – Nelson’s Studio [?], 1963 May (Box 24)
    - Photos – Oak Room, undated (Box 24)
    - Photos – Opening of Graduate Center, 1954 (Box 24)
    - Photos – President Knight’s Inauguration, 1963 (Box 25)
    - Photos – Receiving Institutions Award, undated (Box 25)
    - Photos – Turkish Banquet, undated (Box 25)
    - Photos – Views of East/West Campus, undated (Box 25)
    - Photos – West Campus Kitchen, undated (Box 25)
    - Photos, undated (Box 25)
    - Pine Needles Conference, 1967 Jun (Box 25)
    - Pine Needles Conference, 1969 Aug (Box 25)
    - Pillsbury Mills (Box 25)
    - Plaques (for Gothic Hall & Lancaster House) (Box 25)
    - Plaques – Fraternities (Box 25)
    - Plaques – University Policy (Dining Halls) (Box 25)
    - Plasticware (Box 25)
    - Polymer Symposium, 1964 (Box 25)
    - Position Description Outlines, 1968 (Box 26)
    - Postage Rates, 1958 (Box 26)
    - Pot Sink Proposed Layout, 1968 (Box 26)
    - President’s Reception, 1964 (Box 26)
    - President’s Room, 1970 (Box 26)
    - Price Changes – Dining Halls, 1964-1972 (Box 26)
    - Price Freeze, 1971 (Box 26)
    - Prices, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
    - Prices – Banquet, 1960-1968 (Box 26)
    - Prices – Catering, 1965 (Box 26)
    - Princess Irene of Greece Dinner & Reception, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Procedure for Food Cost Accounting (Box 26)
    - Professors Emeritus (Box 26)
    - Profit and Loss Summaries (Box 26)
    - Project – Union Page Fill-In, 1967 (Box 26)
    - Proposed Subveyor System – University Room, 1969 (Box 26)
    - Proudfoot Co. (Box 26)
    - Purchasing, 1971 (Box 26)
    - Purchasing, 1972-1973 (Box 26)
    - Purchasing – Consumption Reports, 1967-1971 (Box 26)
    - Purchasing – Woman’s College, 1968 Jun (Box 27)
    - Purchasing Agent Food Service – Position Description (Box 27)
    - Purchasing Memos, 1964-1970 (Box 27)
    - Purchasing Prices, 1945-1946, 1948 (Box 27)
    - Quail Roost Conference, 1968 (Box 27)
    - Quail Roost Conference, 1970 (Box 27)
    - Ramsey, Shirley, undated (Box 27)
    - Ramsey, Shirley – Directories (Officers, Faculty, Staff), 1964-1968 (Box 27)
    - Ramsey, Shirley – E.E.O.C. (Mr. Harry Boyte), 1967 (Box 27)
    - Ramsey, Shirley – Grievance Report, 1966 (Box 27)
    - Ramsey, Shirley – Local 77, 1966-1967 (Box 27)
    - Ramsey, Shirley – Newspaper Articles, 1967-1968 (Box 27)
    - Ramsey, Shirley – Personnel File, Schedules, Etc., 1966 (Box 27)
    - Ramsey, Shirley – U.S. District Court, 1969 (Box 27)
    - Rathskellar – Student Union, 1968-1969 (Box 27)
    - Reception – His Excellency Sékou Toure, President of the Republic of Guinea, 1959 (Box 28)
    - Reception – Turkish President, 1954 (Box 28)
    - Red Cross (Box 28)
    - Refrigerators – Men’s Dormitories (Box 28)
    - Remodeling B & C – Background Information, 1961-1963 (Box 28)
    - Remodeling B & C – Cambro, Inc., 1962 (Box 28)
    - Remodeling B & C – Champion Dish Machine Co., 1962-1963 (Box 28)
    - Remodeling B & C – Charles B. Blood, 1960-1962 (Box 28)
    - Remodeling B & C – George E. Hackney, 1962-1963 (Box 28)
    - Remodeling B & C – Mr. Austin Hansen, 1962-1963 (Box 28)
    - Remodeling B & C – Raburn Products (Racks), 1962 (Box 28)
    - Remodeling B & C – Samuel Olson Mfg. Co., 1962 (Box 28)
    - Remodeling B & C – Specifications, undated (Box 28)
    - Renaissance – Newsletter of Duke Young Americans for Freedom (Box 28)
    - Renovation of Subveyor System, 1970-1971 (Box 28)
    - Renovations – Pot Sink, 1965-1966 (Box 28)
    - Renovations – Refrigeration West Campus, 1964-1965 (Box 28)
    - Renovations of Duke Dining Halls (Original Data), 1946 (Box 28)
    - Repairs, 1965-1966 (Box 28)
    - Rescor Industries, 1967 (Box 28)
    - Residence Halls (Undergraduate), 1966 (Box 28)
    - Residence Halls – Summary of Occupancy, 1968-1969 (Box 28)
    - Revere Copper and Brass, Inc., 1959-1960 (Box 28)
    - Robot Room, 1964 (Box 28)
    - Rotation Schedule – East Campus, undated (Box 28)
    - [The] Round Board – Correspondence (Box 28)
    - [The] Round Board – Layout, Architects’ Report, Catalogs, Etc., 1967 (Box 29)
    - [The] Round Board – Report of the University Center Committee to the Educational Facilities Committee, 1964 (Box 29)
    - Russian Students, 1959 (Box 29)
    - Salaries – Higher Education (Box 29)
    - Sales Promotion (DUDH) (Box 29)
    - Sanitation (Box 29)
    - School Leasing Corp., 1965 (Box 29)
    - School of Nursing, 1965-1966 (Box 29)
    - School of Nursing – Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 29)
    - Secondary School Counselors’ Conference, 1964 (Box 29)
    - Seman’s Rehearsal Dinner, 1964-1967 (Box 29)
    - Senior Class Dinner, 1971 (Box 29)
    - Service Pins and Awards (Box 29)
    - Service World Report, 1969 (Box 29)
    - [D.U.] Shelton Management Course, 1970 (Box 29)
    - Signs, 1952 and undated (Box 29)
    - Social Security (Box 29)
    - Southgate (Box 29)
    - Special Events for First Semester, 1974 (Box 29)
    - Special Food Services – Men’s Campus, 1956 (Box 29)
    - Specifications – Grad Center, 1950 (Box 29)
    - Specifications – Grad Center, 1950 (Box 29)
    - Specifications and Proposal – Equipment, 1954 (Box 29)
    - Speed Order Vendors, 1968 (Box 29)
    - Spring Cycle Menus – East Campus, 1974 (Box 29)
    - Staff Conference Business Office, 1965-1966 (Box 29)
    - Staffing Requirements, 1967 (Box 29)
    - Standard Brands, Inc. (Box 29)
    - Statistics (Dining Halls, Price Index, Etc.), 1957-1967 (Box 29)
    - [Dr.] Stead’s Symposium, 1968 (Box 30)
    - Steril Sil – Cost Estimate, 1962 (Box 30)
    - Student Aid (Financial) (Box 30)
    - Student Center – Duke University Development Program (Box 30)
    - Student Employees, 1966 (Box 30)
    - Student Employees – East Campus Dining Halls, 1971-1972 (Box 30)
    - Student Employment (Box 30)
    - Student Employment Applications & Letters (Box 30)
    - Student Employment Memos (Box 30)
    - Student Forms (Box 30)
    - Student Life Symposium, 1964 (Box 30)
    - Student Ratings, 1952-1960 (Box 30)
    - Student Ratings, 1960-1963 (Box 30)
    - Student Sit-In – Allen Building, 1969 Feb 13 (Box 30)
    - Student Union, 1948-1965 (Box 30)
    - Student Union, 1969 (Box 30)
    - Student Union Construction (Box 30)
    - Student Union Nightclub – “The Lookaway”, undated (Box 30)
    - Student Union Welfare Committee (Box 30)
    - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS) (Box 30)
    - Study Showing Effect of Installation of Refrigerators on Usage of Dining Halls by Undergraduate Men, 1966 Dec (Box 30)
    - Subveyor – Blue & White Room, 1971 (Box 30)
    - Summer Administrative Intern Program, 1969-1970 (Box 30)
    - Summer Courses for Employees, 1965 (Box 30)
    - Summer Employment, 1951 (Box 30)
    - Summer Employment – Staff, 1969 (Box 30)
    - Summer Employment for DUDH Employees (Box 30)
    - Summer School, 1951-1970 (Box 31)
    - Summer School – Service of Food East Campus, 1967 (Box 31)
    - Summer Staffing, 1970 (Box 31)
    - Summer Transitional Program, 1969 (Box 31)
    - Supervisor’s Handbook – Duke University (Box 31)
    - Supply Pastors’ School, 1953-1969 (Box 31)
    - Surplus Property, 1951-1971 (Box 31)
    - Surveys (Box 31)
    - Swift & Company (Box 31)
    - Swift & Company – Pro-Tem Beef (Box 31)
    - Syracuse China (Box 31)
    - Tableware (Cost of Individual Items – DUDH) (Box 31)
    - T.C. Cook – Electric Work B & C, 1962 (Box 31)
    - Teer House, 1967 (Box 31)
    - Telephones, 1952-1970 (Box 31)
    - Thanksgiving Buffet, 1964 (Box 31)
    - Thanksgiving Fast for Freedom (Box 31)
    - Thanksgiving Schedule, 1952-1967 (Box 31)
    - Thefts (Box 31)
    - Traffic Commission (Box 31)
    - Training Program – Duke (Box 31)
    - Training Program – Sr. Executive (Box 31)
    - Training Table Menus, Etc., 1956-1971 (Box 31)
    - Training Table, 1960-1962, 1965, 1969-1972 (Box 31)
    - Trash Disposal – Union Building (Box 31)
    - Trinity College Budget, 1971-1972 (Box 31)
    - Turkey Test, 1951-1952 (Box 31)
    - T.V. Program – Mr. Earl Porter (Box 31)
    - Unemployment Compensation, 1973 (Box 31)
    - Union, Local No. 77, 1968-1971 (Box 31)
    - Union Bldg – West Campus – Space Allocation Committee, 1965-1970 (Box 32)
    - Union Building – Alterations, 1953-1954 (Box 32)
    - University Center (Box 32)
    - University “Fact Book”, 1967 (Box 32)
    - University Room – Sales and Promotion, 1970 (Box 32)
    - University Room Remodeling, 1961 (Box 32)
    - Vice President Humphrey Reception, 1965 (Box 32)
    - Vigil, Silent (Duke University), 1968 Apr, 1975 (Box 32)
    - Vigil, Silent (Duke University), 1968 Apr (Box 32)
    - [The] Vigil – Letters Received, 1968 (Box 32)
    - Visitors – East Campus (Box 32)
    - Vocational Rehabilitation (Box 32)
    - Wade [Wallace] Testimonial Dinner, 1967 (Box 32)
    - Wascon Systems, Inc., 1968 (Box 32)
    - Weeks Menu – Cafeteria, 1974 (Box 32)
    - West Campus – Board Plan for Men Students, 1969 (Box 32)
    - West Campus – Job Descriptions (Box 32)
    - West Campus – Management Report, 1967-1968 (Box 32)
    - West Campus – Management Report, 1968-1969 (Box 32)
    - West Campus – Weekly Meal Counts, 1968-1969 (Box 32)
    - West Campus Budget, 1973-1974 (Box 32)
    - Whitford, W.E., - Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 33)
    - Wilson, Dean Mary Grace – Dinner, 1970 Apr 3 (Box 33)
    - Woman’s College – Board of Visitors (Box 33)
    - Woman’s College – Correspondence on Request for Release from Board Obligations, 1967-1968 (Box 33)
    - Woman’s College – Correspondence on Request for Release from Board Obligations, 1968-1969 (Box 33)
    - Woman’s College – Correspondence on Request for Release from Board Obligations, 1969-1970 (Box 33)
    - Woman’s College – Dish Machine, 1952 (Box 33)
    - Woman’s College – Electrical Cooking Layout, 1954 (Box 33)
    - Woman’s College – Feasibility Study, 1965 (Box 33)
    - Woman’s College – Fraternity Groups Visiting (Box 33)
    - Woman’s College – Job Descriptions (Box 33)
    - Woman’s College – Miss Martha Ann’s Course (Box 33)
    - Woman’s College – New Stoves, 1954 (Box 33)
    - Woman’s College – New Refrigeration, 1960 (Box 33)
    - Woman’s College – Recipes (Box 33)
    - Woman’s College – Refund of Board or Permission to Go Off Board, 1969-1970 (Box 34)
    - Woman’s College – Request to Board Increase, 1965-1966 (Box 34)
    - Woman’s College – Tour of Union (Box 34)
    - Woman’s College Campus Center – Duke University (Box 34)
    - Woman’s College Dining Halls – Dean’s House (Box 34)
    - Woman’s College Dining Halls – Food Summary, 1951-1972 (Box 34)
    - [The] Woman’s College Dining Halls – Meal Tickets (Box 34)
    - Woman’s College Dining Halls Correspondence and Data, 1946-1948 (Box 34)
    - Woman’s Student Government Association – Annual Christmas Dinner, 1967 (Box 34)
    - W.S.G.A. (Woman’s Student Government Association) – Report on Pay as You Go (Box 34)
    - Year-Round Operations on Duke University Halls, 1966 (Box 34)
    - Yields of Meat, 1960 (Box 34)
    - Survey of Opinion Concerning the Board System – East Campus, 1971 (Box 35)
- Articles and Speeches,1941-1975
  3.75 ln. ft. (about 2,800 items)
  Arrangement: alphabetically
  The materials in this series include journal articles written by Ted Minah, primarily in College and University Magazine and Institutions Magazine; lectures and speeches by Ted Minah; and articles specifically written about Ted Minah and the various Duke University dining halls and services. Also included are awards honoring both Ted Minah and various Duke University dining halls and its associated services.
  - ACAS (Association of College Auxiliary Services) – Article (Box 36)
  - ACUHO (Association of College & University Housing Officers) – University of Michigan, 1964 Aug (Box 36)
  - Army and Air Force Exchange Service, 1967 (Box 36)
  - Article – Always Consult the Food Services Director in Kitchen Planning (By T. Minah), 1954 Oct (Box 36)
  - Article – Catering is an Important Part of an Inauguration (By T. Minah), 1950 Apr (Box 36)
  - Article – College and University Feeding/An Appraisal, 1964 (Box 36)
  - Article – Eats – Catering Routes (By T. Minah), 1951 Apr (Box 36)
  - Article – Education Doesn’t Stop at Dining Hall Doors (By T. Minah), 1965 May (Box 36)
  - Article – Food Management – NACUFS Technical Bulletin (By T. Minah), 1971 Spring (Box 36)
  - Article – Food Service Directors – Their Function and Training (By T. Minah), 1949 Apr (Box 36)
  - Article – Food Service Planning in Colleges, 1955 Jan (Box 36)
  - Article – How to Buy and How to Sell High Quality Foods (By T. Minah), 1948 Dec (Box 36)
  - Article – Keeping Food Service Costs in Line (By T. Minah), 1951 Dec (Box 36)
  - Article – Organized Management, 1948 Sep (Box 36)
  - Article – Our Catering Services Really Pay Off (By T. Minah), 1956 May (Box 36)
  - Article – Plan for Efficiency (By T. Minah), 1953 Mar (Box 36)
  - Article – Sanitation Belongs in the Planning Phase (By T. Minah), 1958 Jan (Box 36)
  - Article – The Campus Kitchen of the Future (By T. Minah), 1961 Apr (Box 36)
  - Article – There’s an Ideal Way to Plan a University Feeding Facility (By T. Minah), 1953 Aug (Box 36)
  - Article – What a Food Service Director Expects of the Boss (By T. Minah), 1956 Nov (Box 36)
  - Article about Duke Hotel Service, 1955 (Box 36)
  - Article for U.S. Navy Supply Corps Bulletin (Draft), undated (Box 36)
  - Articles Distributed to All Colleges and Universities (Box 36)
  - Articles Written for Lectures at Kentucky (Box 36)
  - Bob Jones University Speech – College Food Service Options in the Sixties, 1960 Nov 2 (Box 36)
  - Boston University Address, 1964 Mar 3 (Box 36)
  - [The] Bulletin of the North Carolina Dietetic Association – Tribute to T.W. Minah, 1973 Spring (Box 36)
  - C and UB (College & University Business) Article – Contract Caterers, 1970 (Box 36)
  - Central Michigan University Lectures, 1967 (Box 36)
  - Central Michigan University Advanced Lectures, 1969 (Box 36)
  - Certificate from Bicentennial Food Service Federation, 1974 (Box 36)
  - Chapel Hill Weekly, 1970 Feb 25 (Box 36)
  - [The] Charlotte News, 1968 (Box 36)
  - Chronicle Clippings, 1945-1963 (Box 36)
  - Chronicle Clippings, 1965-1967 (Box 36)
  - College & University Business, 1956 May (Box 37)
  - College & University Business, 1965 May (Box 37)
  - College & University Business, 1970 Mar (Box 37)
  - College and University Business Articles Written, undated (Box 37)
  - College and University Food Services Institute, 1950 (Box 37)
  - Cornell Lecture, 1951 (Box 37)
  - Divinity School Talk, 1971 Oct 7 (Box 37)
  - Duke Dietetic Interns, Lecture #2, 1968 (Box 37)
  - Duke Dietetic Interns, Lecture #1, 1969-1970 (Box 37)
  - Durham Engineering Club, 1954 Nov 2 (Box 37)
  - Durham Kiwanis Club, 1947, 1958 (Box 37)
  - Durham Sun, 1970-1973 (Box 37)
  - Essentials of Success – Menu Ideas, 1941 and undated (Box 37)
  - Faculty Club Talk, 1952 Feb 14 (Box 37)
  - Food Management Material Used in Writing Article (Box 37)
  - Food Services Executive Association, 1968 (Box 37)
  - Food Services Executive Assn – Charlotte, 1965 Mar 22 (Box 37)
  - Food Services Institute, 1956 (Box 37)
  - Freshman Talk, 1947-1951 (Box 37)
  - Freshman Talk, 1957-1970 (Box 37)
  - George Kraft, 1948 (Box 37)
  - Groen Recipe Contest, 1962 (Box 37)
  - IFMA – Silver Plate Award – Congratulations, 1968 (Box 38)
  - IFMA Conference, 1965 May 21-22 (Box 38)
  - IFMA Symposium, 1970 Feb 17-18 (Box 38)
  - Inplant Magazine, undated (Box 38)
  - Inplant Magazine – Article Written on Duke Dining, 1961 (Box 38)
  - Inplant Food Management, 1961 Mar (Box 38)
  - Inplant Food Management, 1962 Jul (Box 38)
  - Inplant Food Management, 1963 Feb (Box 38)